(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T03:23:42.483755",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ
2nd Round Sales Goods
3期生からの複製直筆コメント入りアクリルパネル
Acrylic Panel with printed hand-written comments from the 3rd Gen members
ファンの皆さんからの応援メッセージ
Support messages from fans
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Vocal cheering is allowed!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
たくさん！
So many!
君のこと
Everything about you,
大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこのハートきっともう止まらない
This overflowing heart surely won't stop anymore!
アイアイアイアイ アイラブユー
I, I, I, I, I love you!
アイアイアイアイ アイニードユー もっともっと
I, I, I, I, I need you, more and more!
...って言わせてて
...let me keep saying it!
きゅるるんハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My heart is bouncing up and down!
雨が降っても雨、雨、雨
Even if it rains, rain, rain, rain...
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない！
Even like this, I still can't escape!
どうしたもんかの ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui, nui, nui!
助けて君だけ あほーいほーい
Save me, only you! Ahoy-hoy!
まった まった まった まった
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
どアニメ宣言！ JOYSOUND
[Text: Extreme Anime Declaration! JOYSOUND]
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった！
and really wanted to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
is so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
全国のアミューズメント施設にてホロライブ3期生プライズ順次展開中！
[Text: Hololive Gen 3 prizes are launching sequentially in amusement facilities nationwide!]
パペットぬいぐるみ (全2種)
[Text: Puppet Plushies (2 types in total)]
寝そべりミニマスコット —ホロライブ3期生— (全4種)
[Text: Nesoberi Mini Mascot —Hololive Gen 3— (4 types in total)]
大判マウスパッド —ホロライブ3期生— (全1種)
[Text: Large Mouse Pad —Hololive Gen 3— (1 type in total)]
詳しくは... キャラ広場 ホロライブ 検索
[Text: Search for "Chara Hiroba Hololive" for details!]
吉野家でごはんしよ
Let's eat at Yoshinoya.
ぎゅう
Beef...
ぎゅう、ぎゅう
Beef, beef...
う〜ん
Mmm...
ぎゅう
Beef...
うま！
So good!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the original's true passion.
牛丼は吉野家
Yoshinoya for beef bowls.
やっぱりこれだな！
Indeed, it has to be this!
ホロライブ3期生ミニCDコレクション
[Text: Hololive Gen 3 Mini CD Collection]
「よくばり電脳ガール」がミニCDコレクションになって登場！
[Text: "Yokubari Cyber Girl" is now a Mini CD Collection!]
2026年1月17日・18日ライブ会場販売！
[Text: Sale at the live concert venue on January 17th & 18th, 2026!]
つながるあるますこっとになって登場！
[Text: Now available as connectable mascots!]
2026年1月17日・18日ライブ会場にて先行販売
[Text: Venue pre-sale on January 17th-18th, 2026]
#さうるる大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推して参る！〜
[Text: #ProjectSayururu ~The strongest idols, here to support!~]
せーの！
Ready, set...
本日は
Today,
ホロライブ3期生ライブ
to the hololive 3rd Generation Live
「きゆるるん大作戦」
"Kiyururun Daisakusen"
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ！〜に
~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But to Stan!~
ご来場いただき…
thank you for coming...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the very end, we have a few announcements to make.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording devices during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
The venue is non-smoking. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Mosh pits, diving, and throwing objects onto the stage...
他の皆様の迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
...or any behavior that causes a nuisance to others or disrupts the performance is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a blast!
はーい！
Okay!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Additionally, cameras for video streaming and photography are present in the venue, so the audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes...
可能性... 可能性がございますので！
There is a... yes, there is a possibility!
あらかじめ、ご了承ください！
Thank you in advance for your understanding!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「きゅるるん大作戦」Day1です！
Also, the live show's hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusenDay1!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd love it if you used the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは、開演まで...
Well then, until the show starts...
もう少しです！
Just a little longer!
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてぺこ！
Let us hear your voices loud and clear, peko!
それじゃ、3期生、エンジン行くかー！
Alright, 3rd Generation, let's rev our engines!
みんな、今からマイクが無くなるので、静かに、静かに...
Everyone, our microphones will be turned off now, so shh, quiet down...
#きゅるるん大作戦
[Title: #Kyururun Daisakusen]
こんぺこ！ 兎田ぺこら
[Usada Pekora: Konpeko!]
不知火フレア
[Shiranui Flare]
こんまっする！ 白銀ノエル
[Shirogane Noel: Konmuscle!]
Ahoy! 宝鐘マリン
[Houshou Marine: Ahoy!]
#きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推しかないでしょ！～
[#Kyururun Daisakusen ~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But To Support Us!~]
あい あい あい あい I love you
"I, I, I, I, I love you!"
もう あい あい あい あい I need you
"I, I, I, I, I need you!"
もっと もっと もっと もっと
"More, more, more, more!"
好きなだけ愛させて
"Let me love you as much as I want!"
3期生ライブ、行くぺこーー！
"3rd Generation Live, let's go-peko!"
みんなで最高の思い出作ろうね！
"Let's make the best memories together!"
うるうるの うるうるの 泣き虫だらけ
"Teary-eyed, teary-eyed, full of crybabies..."
どうかしてるわね 私
"There must be something wrong with me."
心臓ドキドキになってる 警報
"My heart is beating so fast—it's an alarm!"
毎日 幻覚 現れて
"Seeing hallucinations every day..."
頭に花咲いちゃって
"Flowers are blooming in my head!"
恋ってやつは非常識ですわ
"This thing called love is so irrational!"
いっそ食べちゃいたい
"I'd rather just eat you up!"
フリーズした感情
"My frozen emotions..."
誰もが持ってる お願い
"Everyone has a wish."
じゅんじゅん 呪文詠唱
"Pure and innocent, chanting a spell..."
届いて 救助要請
"Reach them, my call for rescue!"
これが恋なら もう後悔しないわ
"If this is love, I won't regret it anymore!"
だから！
"That's why!"
君のこと 大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
"I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!"
溢れるこの愛はきっとずっともっと止まらない
"This overflowing love will surely never stop!"
あい あい あい あい I love you
"I, I, I, I, I love you!"
君が あい あい あい あい I need you
"You are my I, I, I, I, I need you!"
もっと もっと もっと もっと
"More, more, more, more!"
好きなだけ愛させて
"Let me love you as much as I want!"
うるうるハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん
"My teary-eyed heart goes pyon, pyon, pyon!"
おのれに落ちて おらおら
"Falling for you, ora, ora!"
こんなになっても いまだ抜け出せない
"Even in this state, I still can't escape!"
どうしたものかね ぬいぬい
"What should I do, nuinui?"
助けて キャプテン アホイホイ
"Save me, Captain Ahoy-hoy!"
もっと もっと もっと もっと
"More, more, more, more!"
好きなだけ愛してね
"Love me as much as you want!"
ふわふわ浮かぶ 夢の中
"Floating softly in a dream..."
君の声で 目覚めた
"I woke up to your voice."
五感全部が 君のシグナル
"All five of my senses are signals from you."
毎度お騒がせ 5年目
"Making a fuss again, in our fifth year..."
きゅんで壊れちゃいそうだ
"It feels like my heart will burst from excitement!"
恋ってやつは制御不能ですわ
"This thing called love is uncontrollable!"
いっそ抱きしめて
"Just hold me close already!"
壊してもいいよ
"It's okay if you break me."
誰にも邪魔はさせない
"I won't let anyone get in the way!"
ビビビな感情で
"With spark-inducing feelings..."
ギラギラ急展開
"A dazzling, sudden turn of events!"
これが運命なら もう迷わない
"If this is destiny, I won't hesitate anymore!"
覚悟してね！
"Prepare yourself!"
君だけが 大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
"You're the only one I love, love, love, love, love!"
私のこの愛はきっとずっともう離さない
"I'll surely never let go of this love of mine!"
びびび my baby あんど きすきすきすきす kiss me
"Bi-bi-bi my baby and kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss me!"
もっと もっと もっと もっと
"More, more, more, more!"
私だけを見ててね
"Look only at me!"
もしかしたら泣いちゃうかもね
Maybe I'll cry...
だってそんなのぺこぺこちゃん
Because that's Peko-Peko-chan!
わかってるよねダーリン
You know that, right, darling?
いっぱい愛を待ってます
I'm waiting for lots of love!
もっと！ ぺこら！ もっと！ のえる！ もっと！ ふれあ！ もっと！ まりん！ もっと！
More! Pekora! More! Noel! More! Flare! More! Marine! More!
ホロライブファンタジーを... 愛してる！
I love... Hololive Fantasy!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好ーき
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛は ずっと ずっと 戻らない
This overflowing love will never, ever fade.
I I I I I love you 君が
I, I, I, I, I love you, you...
I I I I I need you もっと
I, I, I, I, I need you, more...
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more!
これだけ愛させて
Let me love you this much!
ときめくハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My fluttering heart goes pyon-pyon-pyon!
矢に射たれて おおびょうびょう
Shot by an arrow, oh my!
こんなになったら魔法はとけません
Once it's like this, the magic won't wear off!
本気になってる ぬいぬいぬい
I'm getting serious, nui-nui-nui!
言ってるそばから あほーいほい
Right after saying that, ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more!
これだけ愛してね
Love me just this much, okay?
I I I I I love you
I I I I I need you
私たちの愛をもっと
More of our love!
あ、じゃ ピチピチ？ あほーい！
Ah, then fresh-faced? Ahoy!
ピカチュキ？ あほーい！
Pikachuki? Ahoy!
お色気担当のマリンです
I'm Marine, the sexy one!
よーそろー！
Yousoro!
踊るahoy!に見るahoy!
Dancing Ahoys, watching Ahoys!
たまにドクロくんに配りましょう
Sometimes let's share it with Dokuro-kun!
出航！
Set sail!
はい、船長だぞ！
Yes, I'm the Captain!
うさぎ同盟
Rabbit Alliance!
にんじんもぐもぐ
Carrot munching!
最強女神 ぺこぺこぺこら
Strongest goddess, Peko-Peko-Pekora!
ぺこら！
Pekora!
こらこら
Kora kora!
よしよしして
Comfort me, there, there...
ちょっと よそ見？横取り？
Wait, looking away? Stealing away?
うさぎしか勝たん！
Only rabbits win!
うさぎ力 大成功のために
Rabbit power, for a huge success!
条件コールもいけちゃう？
Can you do the condition call too?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
自己の進化コール
Our self-evolution call!
お決まりのファンサで好き溢れちゃう
Overflowing with love from the usual fanservice!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
極めたオタ芸 踊る
Dancing the ultimate otagei!
新規もいる
There are newbies...
古参いる
There are veterans...
もうはや生きがいなのだ 確定じゃん
It's already our reason for living, that's for sure!
会いたい！ 推したい！
Want to meet! Want to support!
現場でテンプレ応援
Template calls of support at the venue...
きゅるきゅる
kyu-kyu...
ちあー ちあー！
Cheer, cheer!
フレ！ フレ！ エルフ フレ！
Go! Go! Elf, go!
お褒められて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows with praise!
右、左、ハイハイハイ
Right, left, high-high-high!
世界で一番愛してる
I love you more than anyone in the world!
まだチャンネル登録してないなんて無理〜
Not subscribing yet is impossible~
じょいじょい エンジョイ
Joy-joy, enjoy!
団長ののえる
Leader Noel!
ゆるふわの筋肉騎士よ
The soft-and-fluffy muscular knight!
お肉食べたい ウーバーで頼みたい
I want to eat meat, I want to order on Uber!
ぎゅーどん！
Beef bowl!
いつの間に？
Since when?
感謝より愛を頂戴
Give me love rather than gratitude!
これ実質無料！
This is practically free!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
ハートの振り付けも コピる
Copying even the heart choreography!
可愛いとか超えて好きこじらせちゃう
Beyond just cute, I love you and it's complicated!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
概念から愛を集める
Gathering love even from concepts!
ガチ恋勢も
Serious lovers...
遠征組も
Traveling fans too...
もうはや全員仲間決定じゃん
We're all comrades already, that's for sure!
いきたい！ のりたい！
Want to go! Want to ride!
現場で全通応援
Supporting and attending every live show at the venue...
きゅるきゅる
kyu-kyu...
ちあー！ ちあー！
Cheer! Cheer!
みんなの王様！
Everyone's king!
みんなの歌姫！
Everyone's diva!
みんなの団長！
Everyone's leader!
みんなの船長！
Everyone's captain!
トラブルの時も
Even in times of trouble...
推しがへこんだ時でも
Even when your oshi is feeling down...
トライ＆エラー 重ねたい
I want to pile up trial & error...
君と見たい景色があるんだ
There's a sight I want to see with you!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
自己の進化コール
Our self-evolution call!
お決まりのファンサで好き 大好き！大好き！一生好きだよー！
With the usual fanservice, I love you! I love you! I'll love you for life!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
ラストまで追いかける
Following until the very end!
３次元超え存在が最強 大優勝！
Transcending the 3D world, our existence is the strongest, big victory!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅる アイドル
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu idol!
永遠の愛誓う
Swearing eternal love!
単推しも
Solo fans......
箱推しも
Box fans too...
もうはや生涯オタク決定じゃん
Our lives as otaku are already decided, that's for sure!
そうなー！
Exactly!
もうずっと
Forever...
and ever!
現場で限界応援きゅるきゅる
Supporting to the limit at the venue, kyu-kyu!
ちやー！ちやー！
Cheer! Cheer!
一緒に現場で、ちやー！
Together at the venue, cheer!
ふふふ、はーい！
Heheh, hi!
いえーい！
Yay!
いえーい！みんなー！
Yay! Everyone!
ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょっと、はしゃぎすぎたぺこ。
Wait, wait, wait, we got a bit too excited, peko.
ちょっと落ち着こ、落ち着こ。
Let's calm down a bit, calm down.
落ち着くために自己紹介しよう、自己紹介。
To calm down, let's do our self-introductions.
自己紹介オッケー！
Self-introductions, okay!
じゃあ、ぺこらから行きますよ！
Alright, Pekora will go first!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
お前、こんぺこって言わしてやれよ、言いたいやろ！
Hey, let the audience say "konpeko" too, they want to!
ちょっと、もう1回やってよ、もう1回！
Wait, do it one more time, one more time!
なんて言えばいいの？ぺこらは、一応...
What should I say? Pekora, just in case...
「こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー」って言ったら、向こうも言いたいんだよ。
If you say "Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko", they want to say it too.
あ、そういうことね！みんな言ってくれますかー？
Oh, I see! Will everyone say it with me?
じゃあ行きますよ！こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Alright, here I go! Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
おー！
Oh!
ありがとうぺこ！ホロライブ3期生の、兎田ぺこらぺこー！
Thank you, peko! Hololive 3rd generation's Usada Pekora, peko!
はい、じゃあフレアは、こんぬぃじゃなくて、「はい、だい、だいりん」って言うから、「はい、はに」って返してください。
Okay, so Flare won't do "Konnuie", but I'll say "Hi, di, di-ling", so please reply with "Hi, honey".
おー！
Oh!
はい、だいりーん！
Hi, di-ling!
ありがとう！ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアと...
Thank you! Hololive 3rd generation's Shiranui Flare and...
と！
And!
はい、じゃあ、団長は、えー、牛丼は？って言うんで、「波盛り！」って言ってください。
Okay, then Danchou will say, "What about gyudon?", so please say "Namimori"!
大盛りじゃなくて並盛りだから。じゃあ行くよ！
Not large size, but medium size. Alright, here we go!
牛丼はー？
What about gyudon?
あ、そう、そうだよね！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと...
Ah, yes, that's right! Hololive 3rd generation's Shirogane Noel and...
と！
And!
君たち、いま、もしかして、フレアのこと「ハニ」って言った？
You guys... by any chance, did you just call Flare "honey"?
言ってない！おーい、おーい！
We didn't! Hey, hey!
よろよろ...
Wobble, wobble...
団長のこと忘れて、必死な君たち。
Forgetting about Danchou, you guys are desperate.
なんちゃって！えー、じゃあ、どうしようかな。
Just kidding! Well then, what should I do...
普通にあほーいで行きますんで、「あほーい」って言ってくださいね。
I'll just go with "Ahoy" normally, so please say "Ahoy" back, okay?
あほーい！
Ahoy!
誰があほや！
Who are you calling an idiot!
なんちゃって！ホロライブ3期生の...
Just kidding! Hololive 3rd generation's...
えーっと、自己紹介続いてる、宝鐘マリンです！
Uh, continuing the introductions, Houshou Marine here!
いえーい！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
ところでさ、みんななんか、アイドル口上みたいなのさ、ボイス出したやつをやる？
By the way, should we do that idol chant thing that we released as voice packs?
やる、やる！やろうよ、やろうよ！
Let's do it, let's do it! Let's do it!
これはやるしかない！じゃあ順番で？
We have to do this! In order, then?
順番で行きましょう、順番で。オッケー！
Let's go in order, in order. Okay!
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上。
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's chant.
絶対覚えてないぞ。
They definitely don't remember.
覚えてるよね？ちゃんと。
You remember, right? For sure...
覚えてる人、手挙げてー！
People who remember, raise your hands!
あ、結構上がってる！全然上がってないよ。
Oh, quite a few hands are up! Not at all!
全然覚えてないって。
They're saying they don't remember at all!
じゃあ今から覚えてくださいね、じゃあぺこらから行きますよ！
Then please learn it now! Pekora will go first!
ラビット・キャロット・キラッと登場！
Rabbit, carrot, sparkling entrance!
最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！
The strongest idol Pekora has arrived, peko!
まだまだ続くよ、ぺこらすたーと！
There's still more to come, Pekora start!
めっちゃキラキラしてる！
So sparkly!
ちょっと、これめっちゃ難しいんだけど、いけるかな、フレア。
Wait, this is really difficult, I wonder if Flare can do it.
いける、いける！
You can do it, you can do it!
これ、みんなにもコールアンドレスポンスしてほしくて。
I want everyone to do a call-and-response with this.
「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」って言ってください。
If I say "Prepared?", please say "Ready!"
「コールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」って言ってください。
I'll ask "Call?", so please say "Simple!"
手拍子、パンパン！
Clapping, clap-clap!
ステップ、トントン！私は、フレア！
Steps, step-step! I am Flare!
めっちゃ難しいな！
That's so hard!
練習ね！覚えてください。
That was practice! Please remember it.
こんぬぃ！準備は？
Konnuie! Prepared?
コールは？
Call?
手拍子！ステップ！
Clapping! Steps!
私は？
I am?
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd generation, Shiranui Flare!
おー！すごい！ありがとう！
Oh! Amazing! Thank you!
難しいのにすごいですよ！
You guys are great even though it's hard!
じゃあ、次はノエル！
Next up is Noel!
ノエル行きます！
Noel is going!
団長はコールアンドレスポンスないから、ちょっとラップします！
Danchou doesn't have a call-and-response, so I'll rap a bit!
こっから行こうかな。いきます！
Should I start from here? Here I go!
みんなにいつでも、主食！
A staple food for everyone, anytime!
最高の食べ物、答えは牛丼！
The best food, the answer is gyudon!
おろしも飲み物！
Oroshi is a drink too!
みんなの求婚、ダメダメ求婚！
Everyone's proposals... No-no proposals!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル！
Hololive 3rd generation's Shirogane Noel!
え、マリン、ま、コールレスなんで、先に予習しましょうか。
Marine's call and response is next, so let's practice first.
マリンが「マリンは？」って言ったら君たちは「船長！」で、
When I say, "Marine is?" you guys say, "Captain!"
「君らは？」
"And you guys are?"
「一味！」
"Crew!"
「我ら無敵の？」 「海賊団！」
"Our invincible?" "Pirate crew!"
で、最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！」って言うから、そしたら問答無用で「かわいい！」って言う。
And finally, when I say, "Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!" you say "Cute!" without question.
わかりましたね？
Do you understand?
まぁ余裕だよね。はい、素晴らしい。お返事できて、まる。
Well, it's easy for you, right? Yes, wonderful. You answered, correct!
じゃあ、いきますよ！マリンは？
Alright, here we go! Marine is?
船長！
Captain!
君らは？
You guys are?
一味！
Crew!
我ら無敵の？
Our invincible?
海賊団！
Pirate crew!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!
かわいい！
Cute!
いや、気持ちいいね、これ。そんな、かわいいなんて...
Wow, that feels so good! Oh, saying I'm cute...
よかったな、かわいいって言われて、よかったな！そんなことないけど...
I'm glad you were called cute! I'm glad! It's not like that, but...
え、でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと一発目から、もうすごい難しいのやらせちゃって、どうもすみませんね。
But this call and response, sorry for making you do such a difficult one right from the start.
ね、たくさん、ありがとう。ありがとう！
Yeah, thank you so much. Thank you!
え、声が聞こえますよ！
Yes, I can hear your voices!
さっきのさ、私らの円陣聞こえました？
By the way, did you hear our huddle earlier?
聞こえた！やったー！
You heard it! Yay!
ちょっと何か聞こえるかなって不安だったの。
I was a bit worried if you could hear it.
え、こっちにはね、君らの声、よく聞こえるんだけど、
We can hear your voices really well from here,
さすがにマイク通さないとちっちゃかったかなと思って。ね、お腹から出しましたけどね。
but I thought without a mic, our voices might have been too quiet. Yeah, we shouted from our stomachs, though.
あ、聞こえた、ありがとう！
Ah, they heard us, thank you!
聞こえるよ、こっちにも声聞こえてますよ。ありがとう。
We can hear you. We can hear your voices here too. Thank you.
衣装のことも言わなきゃ！
We have to talk about our outfits too!
そうだよ、そうだよ、どうですか？ね、新衣装！
That's right, that's right! How do they look? Yes, our new outfits!
突然の新衣装！可愛いでしょ？
A sudden new outfit reveal! Aren't they cute?
ちょっとずつ違うところがありますので、そうですよ、ぎゅっと見てね。
There are some slight differences on each of us, so look closely.
ぺこらは、耳に輪っかが付いているぺこー！
For Pekora, there are rings on my ears, peko!
なんと、考案者はノエちゃん！そう、ノエル！ありがとう！
And actually, Noel-chan came up with it! Yes, Noel! Thank you!
すごいでしょ？かわいい...
Isn't it amazing? So cute...
え、私はね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほら、こんな感じで、ばつばつばつばつばつ...あ、付いてる。かわいい！
For me, my headdress is, look, like this with Xs... Ah, they are there. Cute!
てへわん！団長は、なんかポンポン付いてます。ポンポン！
Tehe-wan! I have some pom-poms on mine. Pom-poms!
フレアは、頭のこれ、リボンかな？可愛いね！
For Flare, this ribbon on my head? So cute!
あとニーソ違いますね。ルーズソックスだ！そう！
And my knee-high socks are different. They're loose socks! Yes!
そう、フレアはギャルじゃないんでね。あたしらギャル！ぺこらもギャル！ギャルです！
Yeah, since Flare isn't a gyaru. We are gyarus! Pekora is a gyaru too! I'm a gyaru!
ちなみに...何？みなさん、あの...
By the way... What? Everyone, um...
うちらね、結構喋りすぎてるみたいで...
It seems like we've been talking way too much...
音楽、進まないのタイム、みたいな感じなんです。あ、そうだ、そうだ。
Like, we're in "the music won't start" time limit. Ah, that's right, that's right.
でも、ちなみにあの、配信で見てる方、YouTubeで見てる方、概要欄にね、配信チケットのリンクありますので、ぜひ！
But by the way, for those watching the stream on YouTube, there's a link to the stream tickets in the description, so please check it out!
次の曲で、ちょっとチラ見せは...あ、そうだ！終わりペコなので！終わっちゃうので今のうちに！
After the next song, the sneak peek... Ah, that's right! Because this is the end of the free preview! It's ending, so do it now!
まだ、見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんです！お願いします！
There are still so many parts we want you to see! Please!
ハッシュタグ「きゅるる大作戦Day1」でいっぱい呟いてね！呟いてください！
Tweet a lot using the hashtag #きゅるる大作戦Day1! Please tweet!
ていうか、そう、これもやらないと！あのね、生バンドがね、すごいかっこいいじゃない？そう、そうだね。
Wait, right, we have to do this too! You see, the live band is so cool, right? Yes, that's true.
だからちょっと聞かせたくて、じゃあ、ぺこらちゃんから言ってもらっていいですか？
So I wanted you to hear them. Pekora-chan, could you call them out?
了解！うー、エアバンド、キーボード担当、うさだ、ぺこら！
Roger! Keyboard player of our air band... Usada Pekora!
すげえ！かっこいい！めちゃ弾いてる！
Amazing! Cool! He's really playing!
よし、いくよ！ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Alright, here we go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おおー！かっこいい！
Oh! So cool!
はい、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Yes! Drums, Shirogane Noel!
おおー！ドラム！かっこいい！
Oh! Drums! So cool!
じゃあ、フレア、ベースやります！
Then Flare will do the bass!
おおー！かっこいい！最高！
Oh! So cool! Awesome!
はい、うちらが演奏してます！演奏してるよん！
Yes, we are the ones performing! We're playing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲、行きましょうか！行こう、行こう！
Ah, then shall we move on to the next song soon? Let's go, let's go!
あ、場所！場所、場所！あ、こっちじゃない。あ、こっちね。
Ah, our positions! Positions, positions! Ah, not this way. Ah, over here.
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！
Alright, let's head to the next song!
せーの！リアリティ・ファンタジー！
One, two... Reality Fantasy!
Ｈ・Ｏ・Ｌ・Ｏ・Ｌ・Ｉ・Ｖ・Ｅ
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
Ｆ・Ａ・Ｎ・Ｔ・Ａ・Ｓ・Ｙ
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Now, the challenge begins!
冒険 出発 さあ
Adventure, departure!
挑戦 開始 さあ
Now, the challenge begins!
お宝探しに お海原へ出航だ！
Setting sail to the great ocean in search of treasure!
冒険...
Adventure...
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
身も心もぴょんぴょん わくわく頂点上等じゃん
Body and soul bouncing, jumping! Getting excited to the peak is just perfect!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
水平線向こうから 新天地待っててね
From beyond the horizon, a new world is waiting for us!
運命なんか飛び越してその先へ
Leap right over destiny and go beyond!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭間で
Now! Reality, Fantasy, right in the gap between the two!
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に
Sing of your dreams, raise your voice high, together!
さあ まだ見ぬ 世界へと 君を連れていくよ
Now! To a world yet unseen, I will take you there!
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
Our story where everyone connects is about to begin!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
みんなの志 抱き挑む騎士団集合
With everyone's ambitions in our hearts, assemble the chivalric order!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切ってさらに輝け
The sun dwelling in my chest, cut through the wind and shine even brighter!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
迷いと夢 晴天に 掲げたら 突撃だ
Raise our doubts and dreams to the clear blue sky, then charge!
妖精たち この旅 見守って
Fairies, please watch over us on this journey!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭間で
Now! Reality, Fantasy, right in the gap between the two!
帆を上げて 迎えユートピアへ
Raise the sails and head towards Utopia!
さあ それぞれの 世界から 垣根を越えたら
Now! From our respective worlds, once we cross the barriers...
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
Our story where everyone connects is about to begin!
明るく陽気に荒波乗り越え ホロライブ！
Brightly and cheerfully, let's overcome the rough waves! Hololive!
愛嬌開放うさ耳澄まして ホロライブ！
Unleash the charm, prick up your rabbit ears! Hololive!
騎士道と誇り胸に刻んだら ホロライブ！
With chivalry and pride engraved in our chests! Hololive!
神話に伝わる神秘な囁き ホロライブ！
Mystic whispers handed down in myths! Hololive!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, let the challenge begin! Now!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 2つの狭間で
Now! Reality, Fantasy, right in the gap between the two!
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に
Sing of your dreams, raise your voice high, together!
さあ まだ見ぬ 世界へと 君を連れていくよ
Now! To a world yet unseen, I will take you there!
準備はほらできたよ ルートも先決まったよ
Look, we're all ready! The route is already set!
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
Our story where everyone connects is about to begin!
時は2026年
The year is 2026.
2回目の3期生ライブ！
Our second 3rd Gen Live!
このチャンスを逃してなるものか！
No way we're letting this opportunity slip away!
今こそ 全人類
Now is the time for all humanity...
兎化計画を遂行する！
...to execute the Usagification Plan!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!